MUHAMAD NUR ARIF

WEB DEVELOPER | IT SUPPORT

PROFILE SUMMARY

I am a graduate of Vocational High School majoring in Computer and Network Engineering in 2023, and I have decided to continue my education at Mercu Buana University by choosing the Bachelor's degree program in Informatics Engineering. I have experience and achievements in the IT field, one of which is actively participating in certified Bootcamps and winning a championship in an IT competition.

PROFESSIONAL SKILL

I am learning programming languages and implementing my skills by participating in competitions as well as actively joining bootcamps to refine both my soft and hard skills in the field of IT.

TECHNICAL SKILL

I understand programming well in terms of both soft skills and hard skills, especially as I have chosen to become a frontend developer and UI designer due to my interest in interfaces.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Junior IT Support - Part Time

JNE Express, Dadap Residance Kab. Tangerang

- Maintenance hardware and software.
- Repairing office computers and network.
- Assisting in troubleshooting and resolving issues found in computers and networks.

Frontend Developer - Freelance

May 2023 - Present

January 2021 - April 2021

- Developing skills and implementing them in personal projects.
- Serving clients who utilize my services and applying the knowledge I possess.
- Increasing projects and enhancing my personal portfolio for skill development and business growth.

EDUCATION

Vocational High School Yadika 3, Jakarta

Computer and Network Engineering

July 2020 - Apr 2023

Designed and implemented a local area network (LAN) at school, including hardware and software configuration, performance testing, and studied MikroTik as part of graduation requirements.

Mercu Buana University, Jakarta

S1 Information Technology

Sept 2023 - Present

Actively engaged in study groups to collaborate on group assignments, enhancing teamwork and problem-solving skills, and Proactively participated in workshops on web application development to deepen understanding of modern software development.

PORTOFOLIO